<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>footgolf collective</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on footgolf collective</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Sep Dadsetan</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>As We Like It...</title>
      <link>/2018/11/12/as-we-like-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/11/12/as-we-like-it/</guid>
      <description>No sooner met but I kicked, No sooner kicked but I loved, No sooner loved but I putted, But I asked myself the reason, No sooner I knew the reason but sought the birdie and in this degree,have I made a par.
 William Shakespeare (after his first round of Footgolf)   Love&amp;hellip;it’s a word that is used, abused, and overused. In my opinion it should only be uttered in relation to people you care about, with one notable exception&amp;hellip;Footgolf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Footgolf Essentials to Bring Along</title>
      <link>/2018/10/12/5-footgolf-essentials-to-bring-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/12/5-footgolf-essentials-to-bring-along/</guid>
      <description>Origin story It&amp;rsquo;s the night before tournament day, bags are being double and triple checked to make sure nothing is forgotten. In no particular order, I&amp;rsquo;ve came up with a list of 5 things you may not want to forget to throw in your bag before heading out to the course on tournament day.
 Ball Marker A custom poker chip, golf marker, or quarter can be used to mark your ball which must be done when it stops on the green.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uniform of The Sport</title>
      <link>/2018/10/12/uniform-of-the-sport/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/12/uniform-of-the-sport/</guid>
      <description>Origin story Basketball, soccer, and football all are sports with uniforms, right?
FootGolf is not a bit different. The only thing is you get to customize the jersey you wear, however you&amp;rsquo;d like. Instead of your coach forcing you to pick between #98 or #89 because they are the only two left in the gym closet.
We call it the &amp;ldquo;dress code&amp;rdquo; but to be quite frank, it is no different than a personalized uniform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Coast FG Club, 3 time champs!</title>
      <link>/2018/10/12/west-coast-fg-club-3-time-champs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/12/west-coast-fg-club-3-time-champs/</guid>
      <description>Origin story There is nothing else more pleasurable than waking up the morning of competition day in a dreamy hotel. Nerves get the best of you&amp;hellip;or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just the coffee. You have to sprint toward the loo. In your zen, 18 back to back eagles sink and all the podium glory is owned to you.
West Coast FootGolf Club (WC) knows a little thing or two about back to back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description> TBD </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>